<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- titles -->
    <string name="app_name">An Idiot Abroad</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Welcome</string>
    <string name="alt_title_section1">Welcome</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Series 1</string>
    <string name="alt_title_section2">Seven wonders of the world</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Series 2</string>
    <string name="alt_title_section3">The Bucket List</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Series 3</string>
    <string name="alt_title_section4">The Short Way Round</string>
    <string name="tab2_welcome">This season we follow Karl trough the seven wonders of the world! Watch him point out how the great wall of china isn\'t so great, amongst other things.</string>
	<string name="tab3_welcome">This season we follow Karl as Ricky and Stephen send him fullfill other peoples bucket list. Karl does not really like to do things.</string>
    <string name="tab4_welcome">This season we follow Karl trough the footsteps of Marco Polo, and this time he is invited by the friendly little peron, Warrick! Watch as Karl looks forward to seeing Warrick live in the same bad conditions he did last time. (Except this time Ricky and Stephen gives Warrick luxury living.)</string>
	
    <!-- tab menus -->
    <string name="tv_home"><u><b>HOME</b></u></string>
    
    <!-- quotes -->
    <string name="tv_s1q1">I thought I\'d seen the Great Wall of China. Which, being honest with you, it\'s not the Great Wall; it\'s an alright wall. It\'s the Alright Wall of China.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1q2">You know, you can see it for miles - goes on for miles, over the hills and everything. But, so does the M6. Do you know what I mean? You can see that for miles. And you go great. And that does a job. You can drive on that.</string>
    <string name="tv_s1q3">Camels have been around for years. The ships of the desert. That\'s what they\'re known as. We\'ve ended up with Titanic.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1q4">It\'s like a game of Jenga that\'s got out of hand.</string>
    
	<string name="tv_s2q1">I say happiness is like having a cake. If you have a cake every day, you get sick of that cake. If you\'re happy all the time, you get sick of being happy. That\'s a good saying actually. Happiness is like a cake - have too much of it, you get sick of it.</string>
    <string name="tv_s2q2">[Which super power would you have, Karl?]I\'d be bullshit man. There\'s so many meetings going on where, you know people are bullshitting. I\'d just like to walk in. I wouldn\'t need a special costume, just dressed like this and I would fly in and I\'d go, "Bullshit. He\'s talking bullshit." And they\'d go, "Oh. He\'s Bullshit Man." And I\'d go, "Yea. It is Bullshit Man. You\'re talking bullshit." And eventually, people would stop talking bullshit. Anything that\'s going on in the world: A bloke selling a car that\'s knackered, and he\'s going to say it\'s a great one, and it\'s [whoosh] Bullshit!</string>
    <string name="tv_s2q3">Sharks are always dangerous. Jaws, Shark Attack One, Two, and Three. Three films there. There was a chance for him to get friendly. Didn\'t. An angry shark for three films.</string>
    
    <string name="tv_s3q1">You should see the crowds here when Warwick was walking down the street. It\’s the same thing. People just like seeing little oddities in life.</string>
    <string name="tv_s3q2">I will kick a panda in the bollocks if I have to.</string>
    <string name="tv_s3q3">It looks like we\'ve been doing the London marathon and got lost.</string>
    <!-- episode names -->
    <string name="tv_s1e1">  China</string>
    <string name="tv_s1e2">  India</string>
    <string name="tv_s1e3">  Jordan</string>
    <string name="tv_s1e4">  Mexico</string>
    <string name="tv_s1e5">  Egypt</string>
    <string name="tv_s1e6">  Brazil</string>
    <string name="tv_s1e7">  Peru</string>
    <string name="tv_s1e8">  Karl Comes Home</string>
    <string name="tv_s2e1">  Desert Island</string>
    <string name="tv_s2e2">  Trans-Siberian Express</string>
    <string name="tv_s2e3">  Swim with Dolphins</string>
    <string name="tv_s2e4">  Whale Watching</string>
    <string name="tv_s2e5">  Meet a Gorilla</string>
    <string name="tv_s2e6">  Route 66</string>
    <string name="tv_s2e7">  Climb Mount Fuji</string>
    <string name="tv_s2e8">  Karl Comes Home</string>
    <string name="tv_s3e1">  Venice</string>
    <string name="tv_s3e2">  India</string>
    <string name="tv_s3e3">  China</string>
    <string name="tv_s3e4">  A Commentary</string>
	
    <!-- facts -->
	<!-- China -->
	<string name="tv_s1e1f1">  The official name of China is the "People\'s Republic of China".</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f2">  China is the world\'s most populous country.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f3">  China is a single party state governed by the Communist Party.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f4">  China is the world 2nd largest country after Russia.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f5">  Construction on the Great Wall started during the 7th century BCE</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f6">  The Great wall is in fact not visible from the moon.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f7">  Beijing the capital of China has a population of over 20 million.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f8">  Beijing hosted the 2008 Summer Olympics.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f9">  The Forbidden City was the seat of the Chinese emperors for almost 500 years.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e1f10">  There is not language called Chinese. The two most widely spoken languages are called Mandarin and Cantonese.</string>
	<!-- India -->
	<string name="tv_s1e2f1">  The capital of Inidia is New Delhi.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f2">  Two of the world\'s four largest religions originated in India.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f3">  One of the most popular sports in India is cricket.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f4">  The Taj Mahal is in fact a mausoleum.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f5">  The Kumbh Mela festival is the largest peaceful gathering in the world. In 2013 over 100 million people participated.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f6">  India was in colonized by the East India Company in the late 18th and early 19th century.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f7">  The Indian independence movement was lead by Mahatma Gandhi by employing non-violent civil disobedience.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f8">  When India achieved their independence is was split into two countries, India and Pakistan. </string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f9">  India is in constant disputes with Pakistan over the control of the Kashmir region.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e2f10">  India has a thriving film industry, mostly known for their Bollywood films.</string>
	<!-- Jordan -->
	<string name="tv_s1e3f1">  Jordan was created after the first world war and gained independence after the second world war.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e3f2">  Jordan is a constitutional monarchy, King Abdullah II is the head of state.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e3f3">  Petra is an ancient historical city carved into rock in southern Jordan. It is one of the new seven wonders of the world.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e3f4">  Petra is also known as the Rose City because of the color of the rock it is carved from.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e3f5">  The Dead Sea lies between Jordan and Israel. It is the lowest point of dry land on earth at 423m below sea level.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e3f6">  In ancient times Jordan was part of the Persian, and later Mecedonian empire.</string>
	<!-- Mexico -->
	<string name="tv_s1e4f1">  Mexico is the cradle of 2 of the greatest pre-European american civilizations; the Maya, and the Aztec.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e4f2">  The conquest of the Aztecs by the Spanish started in 1519 when Hernán Cortés arrived in Veracruz with 500 conquistadores.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e4f3">  One of the main reasons the Spanish was so effective in conquering the Aztecs was the introduction of smallpox to the American continent.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e4f4">  Mexico gained independence in 1821.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e4f5">  Texas declared independence from Mexico in 1824.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e4f6">  Slavery was abolished in Mexico in 1829.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e4f7">  After the Mexican-American war Mexico was forced to give up over half of its land, including the rest of Texas, California and New Mexico.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e4f8">  Chocolate is originally from Mexico.</string>
	<!-- Egypt -->
	<string name="tv_s1e5f1">  The egyptian civilization started to form when the Sahara began to dry out forcing people to migrate to the Nile.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f2">  Egypt was unified in 3150 BCE by King Menes.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f3">  The Giza Pyramids were created during the Old Kingdom era between 2700-2200 BCE.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f4">  The pyramids were most likely build by paid workers. Not slaves.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f5">  The first time egypt was conquered was around 1650 BCE after 1500 years of native Egyptian rule.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f6">  Egypt created the first religion with only one god.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f7">  The last native pharaoh King Nectanebo was killed in 343 BCE.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f8">  The time between the building of the great pyramids and Cleopatra is longer than the time between Cleopatra and the present day.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f9">  Egypt went through a revolution in early 2011 as part of the Arab Spring.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e5f10">  Cairo, the capital of Egypt is the largest city in the Arab world and in Africa.</string>
	<!-- Brazil -->
	<string name="tv_s1e6f1">  Brazil was claimed by Portugal in April 1500 although it took another 32 years for the colonization to start.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f2">  In 1808 Brazil was elevated from a colony to an official part of United Kingdom of Portugal, Brazil and the Algarves.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f3">  Prince Pedro declared the country\'s independence from Portugal on 7 September 1822.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f4">  The monarchy was overthrown on 15 November 1889.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f5">  The world’s best and most delicious coffee is produced in Brazil.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f6">  Brazil has the biggest rain forest of the world, the Amazon forest.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f7">  Brazil has one of the New 7 Wonders of the World, the Christ Redeemer statue, located in Rio De Janeiro</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f8">  The Carnival of Brazil is an annual festival held during the Friday to the Tuesday before Ash Wednesday.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f9">  The huge parades with the large floats that takes place during the carnival are competitions between samba schools</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e6f10">  The most popular sport in Brazil is football. The Brazilian national football team is ranked among the best in the world.</string>
	<!-- Peru -->
	<string name="tv_s1e7f1">  Peru is the home of the Inca Empire. The largest pre-colombian state in America.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e7f2">  One of the most important remaining Inca sites is Machu Picchu. It was built as an estate for the Inca emperor Pachacuti and is one of the New 7 Wonders of the World.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e7f3">  The Peruvian Amazon forest is populated by several native tribes, some of which used to be cannibals.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e7f4">  In December 1532, a party of conquistadors led by Francisco Pizarro defeated and captured Inca emperor Atahualpa.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e7f5">  Peru declared independence from Spain in 1821.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e7f6">  The Nazca Lines were discovered in 1939.</string>
	<string name="tv_s1e7f7">  Contrary to popular belief the Nazca Lines can be seen from surround hills. Not only the air</string>
	<!-- Desert Island -->
	<string name="tv_s2e1f1">  In 1974, Queen Elizabeth II of Great Britain visited Vanuatu and observed the spectacle of land jumping. The British colonial administration wanted the queen to have an interesting tour, and convinced the Anglican villagers of the Melanesian Mission at Point Cross to do so. However, the vines were not elastic enough because it was the wrong season, the middle of the wet season. One diver had both lianas broken, broke his back from falling, and later died in a hospital. Until 2006, when a diver broke his spine after landing badly and subsequently died in hospital, this was the only fatality in memory.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e1f2">  The construction of the tower typically takes between two and five weeks of labour. Around twenty to thirty men help construct it.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e1f3">  Before land diving the men often bring closure to unsettled business and disputes in case they die.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e1f4">  The first modern bungee jumps were made on 1 April 1979 from the 76 m tall Clifton Suspension Bridge in Bristol, by members of the Oxford University Dangerous Sports Club.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e1f5">  Polynesians settled New Zealand in 1250–1300 CE and developed a distinctive Māori culture. Europeans first made contact in 1642 CE.</string>
	<!-- Trans-Siberian Express -->
	<string name="tv_s2e2f1">  The Trans-Siberian Railway is a network of railways connecting Moscow with the Russian Far East and the Sea of Japan. It is the longest railway line in the world. There are connecting branch lines into Mongolia, China and North Korea.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e2f2">  Full-time construction of the Trans-Siberian Railway began in 1891. Similar to the first transcontinental railroad in the USA, Russian engineers started construction at both ends and worked towards the centre.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e2f3">  Moscow is the capital city of Russia. According to Forbes 2011, Moscow has the largest community of billionaires in the world.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e2f4">  During the French invasion of Russia in 1812, the Muscovites burned the city and evacuated, as Napoleon\’s forces were approaching on 14 September. Napoleon\’s Grande Armée, plagued by hunger, cold and poor supply lines, was forced to retreat and was nearly annihilated by the devastating Russian winter and sporadic attacks by Russian military forces.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e2f5">  Moscow is the heart of the Russian performing arts, including ballet and film. There are 93 theaters, 132 cinemas and 24 concert halls in Moscow.</string>
	<!-- Swim with Dolphins -->
	<string name="tv_s2e3f1">  The most obvious celebration of Songkran is the throwing of water upon others. Thais roam the streets with containers of water or water guns. The throwing of water originated as a way to pay respect to people, by capturing the water after it had been poured over the Buddhas for cleansing and then using this "blessed" water to give good fortune to elders and family by gently pouring it on the shoulder. Among young people the holiday evolved to include dousing strangers with water to relieve the heat, since April is the hottest month in Thailand. This has further evolved into water fights and splashing water over people riding in vehicles.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e3f2">  Muay Thai is a combat sport from the muay martial arts of Thailand that uses stand-up striking along with various clinching techniques. This physical and mental discipline which includes combat on foot is known as "the art of eight weapons" because it is characterized by the combined use of fists, elbows, knees, shins and feet.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e3f3">  The great white shark also known as the great white, white pointer, white shark, or white death, can be found in the coastal surface waters of all the major oceans. The great white shark is mainly known for its size, with the largest individuals known to have approached or exceeded 6 m in length.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e3f4">  More than any documented attack, Jaws directed by Steven Spielberg provided the great white shark with the image of being a "man eater" in the public mind. While great white sharks have killed humans, they typically do not target them: for example, in the Mediterranean Sea there have been 31 confirmed attacks against humans in the last two centuries.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e3f5">  Cage diving is most common at sites where great whites are frequent including the coast of South Africa, the Neptune Islands in South Australia, and Guadalupe Island in Baja California. Cage diving and swimming with sharks is a focus for a booming tourist industry due to its popularity. A common practice is to chum the water with pieces of fish to attract the sharks.</string>
	<!-- Whale Watching -->
	<string name="tv_s2e4f1">  Whale watching is the practice of observing whales and dolphins in their natural habitat. Whales are watched most commonly for recreation but the activity can also serve scientific or educational purposes. A 2009 study, prepared for IFAW, estimated that 13 million people went whale watching globally in 2008.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e4f2">  Organized whale watching dates back to 1950 when the Cabrillo National Monument in San Diego was declared a public venue for observing Gray Whales and the spectacle attracted 10,000 visitors in its first year.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e4f3">  Alaska was purchased from Russia on March 30, 1867, for $7.2 million, $118 million adjusted for inflation at approximately $4.74/km².</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e4f4">  Roald Amundsen\'s expedition to the south pole planned to use around ninety-seven sled dogs. On his first try, two of his dogs froze to death in the freezing temperatures. He tried a second time and was successful. Amundsen was covering 17 miles a day, with stops every 3 miles to build a cairn to mark the trail.  He had 55 dogs with him, which he culled until he had 14 left when he returned from the pole. On the return trip, a man skied ahead of the dogs and hid meat in the cairns to encourage them to run.</string>
	<string name="tv_s2e4f5">  Ice roads are frozen, human-made structures on the surface of bays, rivers, lakes, or seas in polar regions. They allow temporary transport to areas with no permanent road access. Ice roads differ from winter roads in that they are built primarily across frozen waterways. Ice roads may be winter substitutes for summer ferry service. Ferry service and an ice crossing may operate yearly at the same time for several weeks.</string>
	
	<string name="tv_s2e5f1">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e5f2">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e5f3">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e5f4">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e5f5">  </string>
	
	<string name="tv_s2e6f1">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e6f2">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e6f3">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e6f4">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e6f5">  </string>
		
	<string name="tv_s2e7f1">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e7f2">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e7f3">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e7f4">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s2e7f5">  </string>
	
	<string name="tv_s3e1f1">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e1f2">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e1f3">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e1f4">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e1f5">  </string>
	
	<string name="tv_s3e2f1">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e2f2">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e2f3">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e2f4">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e2f5">  </string>

	<string name="tv_s3e3f1">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e3f2">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e3f3">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e3f4">  </string>
	<string name="tv_s3e3f5">  </string>

    <!-- Tab content -->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome blablabl blab balbll abllabl blablalb blalbal blalbala</string>
    <string name="title_activity_episode">Episodes</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

</resources>